//Jan 11 2019
let leadershipDiagram = () => {
	return [
	//NEW LEADERSHIP QUESTIONS BELOW
	{
		"Subject": "Leadership Model",
		"Topic": "Common Goals",
		"Question": "The Leadership Model is the ____________ of AoP?",
		"Answers": [
			"The Foundation.",
			"The Cornerstone.",
			"The Umbrella.",
			"Has nothing to do with AoP."
		],
		"CorrectAnswers": ["The Foundation."],
		"Justifications": [
			"Without the leadership model AoP does not work.",
			"Cornerstones complete and idea. The Leadership Model is more important than that.",
			"The Leadership model does not overshadow AoP.",
			"The Leadership Model is critical to AoP."
		]
	},
	{
		"Subject": "Leadership Model",
		"Topic": "Common Goals",
		"Question": "Common Goals serves what purpose?",
		"Answers": [
			"A meeting charter.",
			"They are the rallying point for everyone in AFSC.",
			"They drive us to “best on the planet” sustainment support.",
			"B & C",
			"None of the above"
		],
		"CorrectAnswers": ["B & C"],
		"Justifications": [
			"Goals do not create charters.",
			"Goals do help rally individuals, but there are other purposes it can fulfill..",
			"Goals do drive us, but there are other purposes it can fulfill.",
			"Goals both drive us and rally people to a common point.",
			"Goals serve an important purpose to AoP."
		]
	},
	{
		"Subject": "Leadership Model",
		"Topic": "Common Goals",
		"Question": "AFSC developed the Leadership Model to communicate:",
		"Answers": [
			"A vision that a leadership culture is the foundation which creates the environment for success.",
			"A new world order.",
			"A methodology for implementing a constraints-based management system.",
			"The Toyota Production System."
		],
		"CorrectAnswers": ["A vision that a leadership culture is the foundation which creates the environment for success."],
		"Justifications": [
			"Without the leadership model AoP does not work.",
			"Cornerstones complete and idea. The Leadership Model is more important than that.",
			"The Leadership model does not overshadow AoP.",
			"The Leadership Model is critical to AoP."
		]
	},
	{
		"Subject": "Leadership Model",
		"Topic": "Common Goals",
		"Question": "What are the desired attributes that create a culture of problem solvers?",
		"Answers": [
			"People, Process, and Resources.",
			"Common Goals.",
			"Speed, Safety, and Quality.",
			"Teamwork, Accountability, Respect, Transparency, Credibility, and Engagement."
		],
		"CorrectAnswers": ["Teamwork, Accountability, Respect, Transparency, Credibility, and Engagement."],
		"Justifications": [
			"These are not attributes.",
			"Goals are what we hope to achieve by incorporating specific attributes.",
			"These are the desired attributes of the workflow, not people.",
			"These attributes create workers who are empowered to solve problems."
		]
	},
	{
		"Subject": "Leadership Model",
		"Topic": "People",
		"Question": "Every workforce needs:",
		"Answers": [
			"Education and Training.",
			"Staffing of 5 employees to a supervisor.",
			"Enthusiastic Attitude Only.",
			"Manuals and online search index for research."
		],
		"CorrectAnswers": ["Education and Training."],
		"Justifications": [
			"Either prior schooling or continual training is essential to maintaining successful workforce.",
			"Workforce needs the proper leadership to accomplish work.",
			"Morale and workforce with the proper skillset is needed for success.",
			"Workforce needs the experience to accomplish work and assist coworkers."
		]
	},
	{
		"Subject": "Leadership Model",
		"Topic": "Speed, Safety, Quality",
		"Question": "Safety is enhanced by:",
		"Answers": [
			"Hoping workforce has common sense to handle whatever safety problems may arise.",
			"Providing safety brochure in employee onboarding packet.",
			"Make sure workforce has sufficient work to keep them busy.",
			"Following regulatory guidance."
		],
		"CorrectAnswers": ["Following regulatory guidance."],
		"Justifications": [
			"Create a methodical/predictable flow.",
			"Constant and engaging encouragement is needed to maintain safe environment.",
			"Create a methodical/predictable flow.",
			"Maintain compliance with agencies, such as OSHA. "
		]
	},
	{
		"Subject": "Leadership Model",
		"Topic": "Cost Effective Readiness",
		"Question": "What is required to reduce the cost to sustain weapon systems?",
		"Answers": [
			"Budget with an extra 10%, to cover unexpected costs.",
			"Understand where money is spent.",
			"Deliver highest quality of product.",
			"Provide all possible resources to accomplish work."
		],
		"CorrectAnswers": ["Understand where money is spent."],
		"Justifications": [
			"Reduce cost of mission execution.",
			"Knowing where all money is used, is necessary to understand where reduction of costs can be adjusted.",
			"Provide affordable product that meets customer requirements.",
			"Reduce waste by providing only what is needed to accomplish work."
		]
	}
	];
}


let littlesLaw = () => {
	return [
	//NEW LITTLES LAW QUESTIONS BELOW
	{
		"Subject": "Little's Law",
		"Topic": "Takt Time",
		"Question": "Takt Time is the reciprocal of Throughput?  True or False",
		"Answers": [
			"True",
			"False"
		],
		"CorrectAnswers": ["True"],
		"Justifications": [
			"Takt Time is the time divided by unit, which is the reciprocal of Throughput.",
			"Takt Time is the reciprocal of Throughput."
		]
	},
	{
		"Subject": "Little's Law",
		"Topic": "Takt Time",
		"Question": "Little's Law and Takt time are flow management tools designed to manage WIP?  True or False",
		"Answers": [
			"True",
			"False"
		],
		"CorrectAnswers": ["True"],
		"Justifications": [
			"These “science of flow” allow you to determine target WIP levels and how fast you must output a product/service with actual WIP.",
			"Both flow management and Takt time can be used to manage WIP."
		]
	},
	{
		"Subject": "Little's Law",
		"Topic": "Flowtime",
		"Question": "What is the Calculation for Flowtime?",
		"Answers": [
			"WIP / Takt Time",
			"WIP * Takt Time",
			"Takt Time / WIP "
		],
		"CorrectAnswers": ["WIP * Takt Time"],
		"Justifications": [
			"WIP = Throughput * Flowtime; divide each side of equation by Throughput to solve for Flowtime.",
			"Flowtime is the amount of WIP multiplied by the rate of items entering the machine.",
			"WIP = Throughput * Flowtime; divide each side of equation by Throughput to solve for Flowtime."
		]
	},
	{
		"Subject": "Little's Law",
		"Topic": "Throughput",
		"Question": "Why is Little's Law Important?",
		"Answers": [
			"Reduces Cost",
			"Reduces manpower",
			"Improves speed and identifies the correct level of WIP."
		],
		"CorrectAnswers": ["Improves speed and identifies the correct level of WIP."],
		"Justifications": [
			"Not a mechanism for calculating cost.",
			"Not a mechanism for calculating labor.",
			"Understanding and utilizing Little's Law will facilitate improving speed by allowing you to determine the correct level of WIP to maximize process speed."
		]
	}
];
}
let radiatorChart = () => {
	return [
	{
		"Subject": "Radiator Chart",
		"Topic": "Execution Elements",
		"Question": "Which item is not a part of the Blue Horizontal Bar Execution Elements?",
		"Answers": [
			"Eight elements for 'set-up' to 'execution'.",
			"Little’s Law Calculation.",
			"Focused on the process machine.",
			"In order from strategic to tactical."
		],
		"CorrectAnswers": ["Little’s Law Calculation."],
		"Justifications": [
			"Elements include \"Road To\", \"Networks\",\"Gates\",\"Release Points\",\"Visual Displays\",\"Standard Work & Scripting\",\"Tools & Regulatory Guidance\",\"Touch Time\" .",
			"Calculation is not a component of Execution Elements.",
			"Execution of incremental steps focused on completing the outcome of the process machine.",
			"Begin at planning and continue to the point of action."
		]
	},
	{
		"Subject": "Radiator Chart",
		"Topic": "Gates",
		"Question": "Gates in the radiator charts refers to:",
		"Answers": [
			"Delivery outcome of process machine.",
			"Continual process flow.",
			"Focused on critical path.",
			"Semi-regular monitoring."
		],
		"CorrectAnswers": ["Focused on critical path."],
		"Justifications": [
			"Refers to discrete increments of work along the critical path.",
			"Contains tangible ending points.",
			"Utilized concepts of critical path for efficient flow.",
			"Requires active and disciplined monitoring."
		]
	},
	{
		"Subject": "Radiator Chart",
		"Topic": "Bottom Four",
		"Question": "What question does the Bottom Four Elements NOT answer?",
		"Answers": [
			"Do actions need to be taken?",
			"Are all systems go?",
			"Do adjustments need to be made?",
			"Who is responsible for sign of on each gate?"
		],
		"CorrectAnswers": ["Who is responsible for sign off on each gate?"],
		"Justifications": [
			"Highlights if further efforts need to be put in place to complete process machine.",
			"Provides active assessment of each element of machine to make sure it is ready for completion.",
			"Helps identify gaps or missed steps that need to be incorporated into process machine.",
			"Not a defined function of the Bottom Four Elements."
		]
	},
	{
		"Subject": "Radiator Chart",
		"Topic": "Leadership Pillars",
		"Question": "Which item is true for what the Leadership Pillars provide?",
		"Answers": [
			"Requires passing familiarity with process machine.",
			"Contains five elements to manage gates.",
			"Creates the environment for success.",
			"Incorporate Quality, without incorporating Speed and Safety."
		],
		"CorrectAnswers": ["Creates the environment for success."],
		"Justifications": [
			"Requires full understanding of the process machine.",
			"Contains Seven elements to manage process machine.",
			"Completion of steps will help provide necessary components for successful completion of process machine.",
			"Also incorporates Speed and Safety."
		]
	}
	];
}
let criticalPath = () => {
	return [
	//NEW QUESTIONS BELOW FOR CRITICAL PATH
	{
		"Subject": "Critical Path",
		"Topic": "Critical Path",
		"Question": "What is critical path?",
		"Answers": [
			"The most critical task on the list.",
			"The path of most resistance.",
			"A sequence for tasks in a project which must be completed on time in order for the project to meet its deadline.",
			"A schedule in a resource-constrained environment."
		],
		"CorrectAnswers": ["A sequence for tasks in a project which must be completed on time in order for the project to meet its deadline."],
		"Justifications": [
			"We are looking at the process as a whole, not just tasks.",
			"The most difficult path is not always the critical path.",
			"The fundamental sequence of tasks is the critical path.",
			"A schedule does not specify time frames or other specifics."
		]
	},
	{
		"Subject": "Critical Path",
		"Topic": "Critical Path",
		"Question": "What is Focus & Finish?",
		"Answers": [
			"A method of polishing an optical lens.",
			"A method of allowing minimum multi-tasking to enable an employee to stay on task to finish the task faster.",
			"Using a microscope to allow you to see your work better.",
			"None of the above."
		],
		"CorrectAnswers": ["A method of allowing minimum multi-tasking to enable an employee to stay on task to finish the task faster."],
		"Justifications": [
			"AoP does not talk specifically about optical lenses.",
			"With minimal multi-tasking employees can Focus on one task and Finish faster.",
			"Not all work tasks require a microscope.",
			"One of the answers is correct."
		]
	},
	//TYPOS VVVVVVVV
	{
		"Subject": "Critical Path",
		"Topic": "Critical Path",
		"Question": "You and your team have identified the critical path and are monitoring progress.  You realize that work has stopped at one step and there is no work around despite your team’s best efforts. Your project is “off critical path” and will be late to the targeted deadline.  You should?",
		"Answers": [
			"Panic.",
			"Declare an Andon to elevate the constraint to your leadership for help in resolving it.",
			"Blame someone.",
			"Ask for overtime."
		],
		"CorrectAnswers": ["Declare an Andon to elevate the constraint to your leadership for help in resolving it."],
		"Justifications": [
			"Panicking is never recommended.",
			"Leadership has the ability to resolve issues that employees sometimes cannot.",
			"This does not solve the problem, but uses valuable time and resources.",
			"More time is not guaranteed to solve the problems and only treats the symptoms of the issue."
		]
	},
	{
		"Subject": "Critical Path",
		"Topic": "Critical Path",
		"Question": "You are the project manager for your organization and are creating a project schedule.  You know that the project will have required steps that will compete for some scarce resources – one of your teammates has a specific skill that no one else has.  Two other steps in your project will be competing for the same piece of equipment at the same time.  Under this resource-constrained environment, what management approach should you use?",
		"Answers": [
			"Critical Path.",
			"Critical Chain.",
			"There is not specific methodology need just as long as you meet the schedule."
		],
		"CorrectAnswers": ["Critical Chain."],
		"Justifications": [
			"Critical path describes the events in at process.",
			"Critical chain focuses on the management of resources in situations like these.",
			"Not all methodologies are created equal."
		]
	},
	{
		"Subject": "Critical Path",
		"Topic": "Critical Path",
		"Question": "The Radiator Chart Horizontal Bars depict:",
		"Answers": [
			"Complicated steps.",
			"A “playbook” of step by which you can implement AoP effectively.",
			"A list of tasks that you must get approval to address.",
			"None of the above."
		],
		"CorrectAnswers": ["A “playbook” of step by which you can implement AoP effectively."],
		"Justifications": [
			"AoP is supposed to be simple.",
			"Playbooks give an overall view of how to accomplish goals",
			"Tasks should not need approval to address, only approval to complete.",
			"One of the answers are correct."
		]
	},
	{
		"Subject": "Critical Path",
		"Topic": "Critical Path",
		"Question": "The Bottom four elements of the Radiator chart are a lighter blue color to highlight:",
		"Answers": [
			"These four steps should be contracted out.",
			"Focused on the tactical elements of a process that the doer accomplishes.",
			"Focused on the strategic elements of the process that the leadership should accomplish."
		],
		"CorrectAnswers": ["Focused on the tactical elements of a process that the doer accomplishes."],
		"Justifications": [
			"AoP helps your area, not identifying contracted steps.",
			"Correct",
			"The chart should be for all those who are working on the task."
		]
	},
	];
}

let questionFunctionNames = [leadershipDiagram, littlesLaw, radiatorChart, criticalPath];
